https://fourwheelcampers.com/online-privacy-policy/

Skip NavigationOnline Privacy PolicyFour Wheel Campers, LLC values its users’ privacy. This Privacy Policy will help you understand how we collect and use personal information from those who visit our website or make use of our online services, and what   we will   and   will   not do with   the information we collect. Our Policy has been designed and created to assure those affiliated with Four Wheel Campers, LLC of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet, but to exceed, most existing privacy standards.We reserve the right to make changes to this Policy at any given time. If you want to make sure that you are up to date with the latest changes, we advise you to frequently visit this page. If at any point in time Four Wheel Campers, LLC decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.This Policy applies to Four Wheel Campers, LLC, and it governs any and all data collection and usage by us. Through the use of HTTPS://fourwheelcampers.com, you are therefore consenting   to the data collection procedures expressed in this Policy.Please note that this Policy does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that Four Wheel Campers, LLC does not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by us. If you visit a website that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information. It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent to better understand the way in which websites garner, make use of and share the information collected.Specifically, this Policy will inform you of the followingWhat personally identifiable information is collected from you through our website;Why we collect personally identifiable information and the legal basis for such collection;How we use the collected information and with whom it may be shared;What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data; andThe security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your Information We CollectIt is always up to you whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us, although if you elect not to do so, we reserve the right not to register you as a user or provide you with any products or services. This website collects various types of information, such as:Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card information etc. which may be used when you purchase products and/or services and to deliver the services you have requested.In addition, Four Wheel Campers, LLC may have the occasion to collect non-personal anonymous demographic information, such as age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and religion, as well as the type of browser you are using, IP address, or type of operating system, which will assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.Please rest assured that this site will only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide to us by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested, and any additional uses specifically provided for on this Policy. Why We Collect Information and For How Long We are collecting your data for several reasons:To better understand your needs and provide you with the services you have requested;To fulfill our legitimate interest in improving our services and products;To send you promotional emails containing information we think you may like when we have your consent to do so;To contact you to fill out surveys or participate in other types of market research, when we have your consent to do so;To customize our website according to your online behavior and personalThe data we collect from you will be stored for no longer than necessary. The length of time we retain said information will be determined based upon the following criteria: the length of time your personal information remains relevant; the length of time it is reasonable to keep records to demonstrate that we have fulfilled our duties and obligations; any limitation periods within which claims might be made; any retention periods prescribed by law or recommended by regulators, professional bodies or associations; the type of contract we have with you, the existence of your consent, and our legitimate interest in keeping such information as stated in this Policy. Use of Information Collected Four Wheel Campers, LLC does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of its customer lists and/or names to any third parties.Four Wheel Campers, LLC may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from https://fourwheelcampers.com.Four Wheel Campers, LLC may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered. Disclosure of InformationFour Wheel Campers, LLC may not use or disclose the information provided by you except under the following circumstances:as necessary to provide services or products you have ordered;in other ways described in this Policy or to which you have otherwise consented;in the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity cannot reasonably be determined;as required by law, or in response to a subpoena or search warrant;to outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential;as necessary to enforce the Terms of Service;as necessary to maintain, safeguard and preserve all the rights and property of Four Wheel Campers, LLC. Non-Marketing PurposesFour Wheel Campers, LLC greatly respects your privacy. We do maintain and reserve the right to contact you if needed for non-marketing purposes (such as bug alerts, security breaches, account issues, and/or changes in Four Wheel Campers, LLC products and services). In certain circumstances, we may use our website, newspapers, or other public means to post a notice. Links to Other WebsitesOur website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. Four Wheel Campers, LLC does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website. Notice to European Union UsersFour Wheel Campers, LLC’s operations are located primarily in the United States. If you provide information to us, the information will be transferred out of the European Union (EU) and sent to the United States. (The adequacy decision on the EU-US Privacy became operational on August 1, 2016. This framework protects the fundamental rights of anyone in the EU whose personal data is transferred to the United States for commercial purposes. It allows the free transfer of data to companies that are certified in the US under the Privacy Shield.) By providing personal information to us, you are consenting to its storage and use as described in this Policy. SecurityFour Wheel Campers, LLC takes precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (e.g. credit card information), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the webpage.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.   The computers and servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. This is all done to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.The company also uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications to build users’ trust and confidence in the internet and website use by providing simple and secure access and communication of credit card and personal information. Acceptance of TermsBy using this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you agree and acceptance of such changes. How to Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.Email: customerservice@fourwh.com Telephone Number: 530-666-1442 Mailing Address:Four Wheel Campers, LLC 109 Pioneer Ave Woodland, California 95776 We wish for health for you and your families! Happy Holiday to all of our friends, family, and employees. 2020 began with a high level of interest and momentum – which has continued into late Fall. However, to ensure our high quality standards are not compromised, we have resisted the temptation to grow too fast. This has resulted in historically long lead times. We encourage you to to connect with your nearest dealer so that you discover when to place your order in time to meet your 2021 trip needs. Here’s to your future trips and adventures, and thank you for considering us to ride along with you! Team Four Wheel CampersSign-up for our NewsletterGet the news on product reveals, events, and videos
Leave this field empty if you're human:
